fasttimesatnaupage.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Statement | National American University

******Introduction**  
National American University recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy and the information that you share with us. Described below is our policy on the collection, use, disclosure, maintenance and protection of personal information that you provide to us through this website.

**Collection of Information**  
The information that we collect from you through this website will vary depending upon how you use the website and what information you choose to provide to us. Generally, we collect any information that you provide to us through online registrations and applications, participating in games and other activities, posting information on bulletin boards, or other forms of correspondence.

We may also use "cookies" or "scripts" to collect information about your use of the website. You may adjust your Internet browser to disable the use of cookies and scripts; however, some features of this website may not be available without the use of cookies and scripts.

**Your Choice**  
When we obtain personal information from you, we will provide you with the opportunity to "opt-out" of any use of your information in ways unrelated to fulfilling your requests for information or processing your application for admissions. If you later decide to "opt-out" of such uses, you may do so by contacting us at the following address: [nausupport@national.edu](mailto:nausupport@national.edu).

**Use of Information**  
We use information collected from you for four general purposes: to personalize your online experience when using this website, to send you personalized correspondence, to fulfill your requests for certain information, and to process your application for admissions.

**Distribution of Information**  
We do not disclose any personal information collected from you other than to our agents and contractors for the purposes described above. We may, however, disclose information concerning our website and its users in aggregate, non-personally identifiable form.

**Security**  
We use industry-standard security measures to protect any personal information that you may provide to us. However, we cannot guarantee that your submissions to our website, any content residing on our servers, or any transmissions from our server will be completely secure.

**Access to Your Information**  
Maintaining information that is current, accurate and complete allows us to make our website more useful. To that end, we encourage you to update your information from time to time. To review the information that we have concerning you and your use of this website, please contact us at the address set forth above.
